export const qAndA: Array<{ question: string; answer: string }> = [
  {
    question:
      'of a thing against or without reason or propriety incongruous unreasonable illogical',
    answer: 'asburd',
  },
  {
    question:
      'arousing or deserving mockery or derision absurd preposterous risible',
    answer: 'ridiculous',
  },
  {
    question: 'void or destitute of sense silly senseless empty headed',
    answer: 'inane',
  },
  {
    question: 'suitable for comedy trivial coarse low undignified',
    answer: 'comical',
  },
  {
    question:
      'contrary to nature reason or common sense monstrous foolish perverse',
    answer: 'preposterous',
  },
  {
    question:
      'suited to occasion derisive laughter ridiculous laughably absurd',
    answer: 'ludicrous',
  },
  {
    question:
      'extremely ludicrous that is matter only for laughter absurdly futile',
    answer: 'farcical',
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answer: '',
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answer: '',
  },
  {
    question: '',
    answer: '',
  },
];
